<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food For Thought on Brian James Advisory</title>
    <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/categories/food-for-thought/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food For Thought on Brian James Advisory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 11:45:10 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/categories/food-for-thought/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amplify Your Mindset</title>
      <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/amplify-your-mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 11:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/amplify-your-mindset/</guid>
      <description>Hi dear,
In this note I will be telling you a special technique. I would call this Mindset Amplification, which helps you to increase trust, prosperity and in other words, present the huge values of yourself.
One of my readers, John, asked me, &amp;ldquo;Thank you so much for your kind help and sharings. I usually follow you to read the posts. At times when I turned off my computer to sleep but noticed your new post, I still stayed up and finish them even though I was so sleepy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honesty Is The Sexiest Charm</title>
      <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/honesty-is-the-sexiest-charm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 11:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/honesty-is-the-sexiest-charm/</guid>
      <description>Oh dear,
In previous sessions, we have discussed about some fundamental mistakes guys usually make on their journeys to win the ladies of their lives. How about today? I will be talking about Honesty. The Honesty of Men.
Well, what makes you think about honesty? Currently how many definitions are there in your own dictionary? Where does honesty stand in your life&amp;rsquo;s priority?
To me, honesty is the key that enables me successes with ladies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Men: Don&#39;t Make These Mistakes</title>
      <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/men-dont-make-these-mistakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 11:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/men-dont-make-these-mistakes/</guid>
      <description>My brothers,
Last month I had a day trip with my friends and need the mountain bike. But then I realised there was a small problem with the gear of my mountain bike, so I took my tools and tried to fix it (my first attempt ever). Well, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know why but after a while of trying hard, my bike was totally spoilt. Sign. Quite disappointing there. After all I had to rush to the bike shop to get another total new one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Admit It</title>
      <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/admit-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 11:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/admit-it/</guid>
      <description>My brothers, today I will be talking about one thing, one action, that is
&amp;ldquo;Admit it.&amp;rdquo;
Yes, that is the way which helped me achieve a lot of successes, not just with ladies. In the years living this life, I have never met a strong person with an easy past. And, a man would never go from zero to hero if he does not overcome one challenge, just to admit he is weak at it, and needs help.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>