<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food For Thought on Brian James Advisory</title>
    <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/categories/food-for-thought/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food For Thought on Brian James Advisory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 11:45:10 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/categories/food-for-thought/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>When You Are Lost</title>
      <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/when-you-are-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 11:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/when-you-are-lost/</guid>
      <description>1. Believe that your calling is closer than you think.
We spend so much time thinking about what our calling is and how we will fulfill it instead of trying to follow our curiosity or the excitement we feel towards something over the other.
2. Our calling may not be life-changing, but it guides our steps in the right direction.
A lot of people think their calling has to be something extraordinary or magical, but sometimes our calling may be very real and ordinary but it has the potential to make our lives extraordinary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Have All The Good Guys Gone</title>
      <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/where-have-all-the-good-guys-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 11:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/where-have-all-the-good-guys-gone/</guid>
      <description>Dear Women,
Stop.
Stop looking for men.
Not on Tinder. Not at work. Not through mutual friends. Not on Facebook. Not even at parties.
You need to stop looking for men at all the wrong places.
Because you may not have realized it yet, but, the right men are right in front of you.
The right men for you aren&amp;rsquo;t the ones shown in movies or written about in books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amplify Your Mindset</title>
      <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/amplify-your-mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 11:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/amplify-your-mindset/</guid>
      <description>Hi dear,
In this note I will be telling you a special technique. I would call this Mindset Amplification, which helps you to increase trust, prosperity and in other words, present the huge values of yourself.
One of my readers, John, asked me, &amp;ldquo;Thank you so much for your kind help and sharings. I usually follow you to read the posts. At times when I turned off my computer to sleep but noticed your new post, I still stayed up and finish them even though I was so sleepy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Actually The Way You Say</title>
      <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/its-actually-the-way-you-say/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 11:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/its-actually-the-way-you-say/</guid>
      <description>Brothers,
In communication, especially with women, the gesture and the body language are much more important than the thing we say. Many, many times more. Do you know that, in reality, body language comprises up to 93% of the communication power, while the message is just little 7%.
Yes, that is true. Body language is the key factor deciding a winner or loser, not the message my friend.
So, what does body language comprise of?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honesty Is The Sexiest Charm</title>
      <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/honesty-is-the-sexiest-charm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 11:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/honesty-is-the-sexiest-charm/</guid>
      <description>Oh dear,
In previous sessions, we have discussed about some fundamental mistakes guys usually make on their journeys to win the ladies of their lives. How about today? I will be talking about Honesty. The Honesty of Men.
Well, what makes you think about honesty? Currently how many definitions are there in your own dictionary? Where does honesty stand in your life&amp;rsquo;s priority?
To me, honesty is the key that enables me successes with ladies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Men: Don&#39;t Make These Mistakes</title>
      <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/men-dont-make-these-mistakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 11:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/men-dont-make-these-mistakes/</guid>
      <description>My brothers,
Let me tell you a story. Last month I had a day trip with my friends and need the mountain bike. But then I realised there was a small problem with the gear of my mountain bike, so I took my tools and tried to fix it (my first attempt ever). Well, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know why but after a while of trying hard, my bike was totally spoilt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Admit It</title>
      <link>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/admit-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 11:45:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brianjamesadvisory.github.io/admit-it/</guid>
      <description>My brothers, today I will be talking about one thing, one action, that is
&amp;ldquo;Admit it.&amp;rdquo;
Yes, that is the way which helped me achieve a lot of successes, not just with ladies. In the years living this life, I have never met a strong person with an easy past. And, a man would never go from zero to hero if he does not overcome one challenge, just to admit he is weak at it, and needs help.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>